Hello.
こんにちは
She's an amazing beauty.
ものすごい美人さんだね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
What is your name?
お名前は何て言うんですか?
This is Hikari.
ヒカリです
Hikari-chan.
ヒカリちゃん
nice to meet you.
初 めまして
初めまして
How old is Hikari-chan?
ヒカリちゃんは何歳ですか?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
You're young.
若いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Hikari-chan, have you ever taken a photo shoot like this?
ヒカリちゃんこういう撮影はしたことある?
It's my first time so I'm nervous.
初めてなので緊張してます
It looks like you're really excited.
すごいドキドキしてそうだね
yes.
はい
I'm so excited, she's such a beauty.
ドキドキしてるかも、すごい美人
What do you usually do, Hikari-chan?
普段は何してるの、ヒカリちゃんは?
I usually go to a vocational school.
普段は専門学校に通ってます
I went to a vocational school.
専門学校行ってんだ
yes.
はい
Vocational school is quite difficult.
専門学校って結構大変だよね
I agree.
そうですね
I'm busy every day.
毎日忙しいです
Do you go every day?
毎日行ってんの?
I go there about 5 times a week.
週5ぐらい行ってんだ
I'm busy.
忙しいな
busy.
忙しい
Do you specialize in something fashionable?
なんかオシャレな専門行ってんの?
I'm doing nursing.
看護行ってます
nursing?
看護?
That's really surprising.
めちゃくちゃ意外だね
is that so.
そうですか
That's right.
そうなんだ
She's going to nurse with this look.
このルックスで看護行くんだね
I thought it was apparel or something like that.
アパレルとかそっちかと思った
It's nursing.
看護なんです
That's what I'm interested in.
そういうのに興味あるんだ
I agree.
そうですね
You're very serious.
すごい真面目なんだね
That's not the case though.
そんなことないけど
Yeah.
うん
Hikari-chan, what do you usually do on your days off?
ひかりちゃんはさ、 普段休みの日とか何やってるの?
I usually play with friends and go shopping.
普段はお友達と遊んだり、 お買い物行ったりすることが多い
is.
です
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
Are you playing with your friends? How many people are playing with them?
友達と遊んでるの、それ何人ぐらいが遊ぶの?
I guess there are quite a lot of people.
結構人数が多いかな
Ah, so you have a lot of friends.
あ、じゃあ友達多いんだね
Yes, that may be true.
うん、そうかもしれない
Hey.
へー
We go shopping together there.
お買い物とか一緒に行くんだね、そこで
I'm going.
行 きます
There's no way you're alone?
一人だってわけないの?
Not much.
あんまり
I probably play games alone at home a lot.
お家で一人で ゲームすることも多いかな
Hey, you like games.
へ ー、ゲーム好きなんだね
Something seems wrong.
なんかやんなそう
Looks like they're doing something like tsumutsumu.
つむつむとかやってそう
Old game.
昔のゲーム
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏はいるのかな?
I'm not there right now.
今いないです
Why don't you make it?
なんで作んないの?
Even though it's so cute.
こんな可愛いのに
Can't you?
できない?
It's not like I'm enjoying my free time or anything like that.
フリーを満喫してるとか、 そういうわけじゃなくて
That's not the case.
そういうわけじゃないです
want.
欲しい
I want a wish.
願望欲しいんだよ
To.
へ ー
Hikaru-chan, what kind of man do you like?
ヒカルちゃん、どういう男の人が好きだろう?
I agree.
そうですね
I think I like tall people with nice smiles.
笑顔が素敵で、 身長高い方が好きかな
Hmm.
う ーん
Approximately how many centimeters?
だいたい何センチくらい?
180?
About 180.
180くらいか
It's not that common among Japanese people.
結構日本人だとあんまりないね
I agree.
そうですね
Is that so?
そう か
I like being tall.
背高いのが好きなんだね
How many boyfriends have you had so far?
今まで彼氏は何人いるの?
Until now, there are only three people.
今までは3人しかいないです
boyfriend?
彼氏?
yes.
はい
Why is there so little?
なんでそんな少ないの?
I couldn't.
できなかった
Is one person long?
一人が長い?
I agree.
そうですね
I wonder if that's also the case.
それもあるかな
Will it last forever?
どんがり続くの?
roughly.
大体
The longest was two and a half years.
一番長くて2年半
It's long.
長いね
長いです
It's been 18 years, 2 and a half years, about 3 people.
18年、2年半、3人くらいだよね
That's going to happen.
そうなっちゃうね
What is the free period?
フリーの期間とかは?
there is.
あります
Do you play with men in such cases?
そういうときは男の人と遊ぶの?
Maybe not.
そうでもないかも
Play sometimes.
たまに遊んで
What is that?
それ何?
Do you also have sex?
エッチもするの?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Good, that.
いいな、それ
That's right.
そうなんだ
So now it's free.
じゃあ今はフリーで
Yeah.
うん
I guess you're enjoying it to the fullest.
満喫してるわけだね
But it doesn't seem like he's playing like that.
でもそんな遊んでるわけでもなさそうだね
Not really.
そうでもない
Even though it's so cute.
こんな可愛いのにね
It's really rare.
すごいレアじゃん
If it were me, I'd play around.
俺だったら遊び尽くすけど
I see.
なるほどね
Up until now, in that experience, there was some strange kind of sex.
今までさ、その経験の中で なんか変わったエッチとかってあった
Did you do it?
り した?
This was exciting.
これ興奮したなとか
What I did outside.
外でしたこと
Where did you do it?
どこやったの?
公園
People taking a walk.
お散歩してる人とか
That's erotic.
エロいな、それ
I just wanted to see it.
ちょっと見たかったな
Why didn't you tell me?
なんで教えてくれなかったの?
It probably burned outdoors.
や っぱ野外燃えたか
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
I see.
なるほどね
Your skin is pure white.
肌真っ白だね
That's not true.
そんなことないね
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立ってみてよ
Great style too.
すごいスタイルもいいじゃん
I see.
そうか
Do you usually go on a diet?
普段ダイエットとかしてるの?
It's not like I eat ramen every day.
全然、毎日ラーメンって感じ
Really?
ほんとに?
I'm jealous, I'm not fat.
羨ましいね、太んなくて
I'll gain weight.
太ります
Really?
ほんとか
Look behind you?
後ろ見てみ?
Hikari-chan, what do you like about your body?
ひかりちゃんさ、 自分の体どこが好き?
Do you like the head spirit?
首霊が好きかな?
Shouli?
首霊?
Her ass is kind of plump, and she has an erotic-looking butt.
なんかお尻もプリプリしてて、 エロそうなお尻してるけど
It's small, so not much.
ちっちゃいから、あんまり
Is it small?
ちっちゃいの?
Flirt around a little.
ちょっとフリフリして
While looking at me.
こっち見ながら
Shake your butt.
お尻振ってよ
cute?
可愛い?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Try wrapping your skirt around it a little.
それちょっとスカート巻くってみてよ
this?
これ?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Just a little more.
もうちょい
Erotic.
エロ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいね
I lost my butt.
お尻取れちゃったね
Shall I list some more?
もうちょっと挙げてみよっか
more than this?
これ以上?
More than that.
それ以上
Kuro-chan, what do you think?
黒ちゃん、どう?
This ass.
このケツ
You want to lick this, right?
舐めたいでしょ、これ
Just look at my face.
顔だけこっち見て
That's a bloody ass.
血のお尻だなぁ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look here.
こっち見てほら
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
This neck and breasts look like each other, so could you please take it off for a while?
この首るとおっぱいみたいから、ちょっと脱がしてもらえた?
Look at this person's face.
見て、この人の顔
It's cute.
可愛いね
Please say hello to Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃんによろしくね
please.
お願いします
Be careful, he's a real pervert.
本当の変態だから気をつけてな
cheers.
乾杯
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Is there something so erotic about One Piece company?
そんなワンピースの社にこんなエロいのは何かあったのかな?
It's because it's erotic.
エロいからだよな
Aren't these breasts big?
これおっぱいでかくない?
How many cups are there?
何カップあるの?
Is there a D?
Dあるかな?
D cup?
Dカップ?
All angles are cute too.
すべての角度も可愛いね
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
Celebrities.
芸能人や
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Shall I take pictures of every corner?
隅々前撮っちゃおうか
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Take this off too.
これも脱がして
It's really stylish.
めちゃくちゃスタイルいいじゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Harsh.
えぐ
Kuro-chan, this is terrible.
黒ちゃん、これはやばいな
This face and this body.
この顔とこの体
This is going to blow my mind.
ボッキしちゃうね、これ
She's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ美人だわ
Peace.
ピースして
piece?
ピース?
Yeah.
うん
Turn around again.
もう一回後ろ向いて
Put your hand next to it.
そのそばに手ついて
Show me your butt.
お尻ぷりっとこっちつけ出して
Open your legs.
足開いて
Stick it out more, butt.
もっと突き出して、お尻
The waist is amazing too.
くびれもすごいね
You like the waist, right?
くびれ好きなんでしょ?
own.
自分の
Yeah.
うん
Show me off.
見せつけてよ
You have the body of an erotic woman.
エロい女の体してるね
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
yes.
はい
Where do you want to see?
どこ見たい?
Hikari-chan's.
ヒカリちゃんの
Want to see boobs?
おっぱい見たい?
So, can I like this too?
じゃあ、こっちも好きにしていいですか?
I'm getting nervous.
緊張しちゃうね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Great style.
すんごいスタイル
Wow, beautiful breasts.
すんげえ綺麗なおっぱい
Why did you look away?
なんで目をそらしたの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm really drunk though.
めちゃくちゃ酔ってるけど
She has a really erotic body.
めちゃくちゃエロい体してるわ
I want to talk too much, Kuro-chan.
喋りすぎたいね、黒ちゃんこれ
Raise it up like this.
こうやって上で上げて
both hands.
両手
Hold me.
抱えて
Elbow to elbow.
肘と肘で
Are you sweating?
汗かいちゃった?
汗かいたの?
I'm nervous.
緊張して
Because that's my favorite.
それ大好物だから
Raise it like this.
こうやって上げて
both.
両方
Hold your elbows like this.
肘と肘持ってこうやって
Elbow to elbow?
肘と肘?
Like this.
こうやって
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
It seems like she's nervous and her armpits are wet.
緊張して脇濡れてるらしいから
I'm sweating.
汗かいてる
Can I have a chew?
チューしてもらえる?
This cute sweat.
この可愛いこの汗
Can you lick me?
ペ ロペロしてもらえる?
Isn't it delicious?
美味しいでしょ?
Because I like this face.
こんな顔がいいから
It's embarrassing.
恥 ず かしい
Have you ever had your armpits licked?
脇舐められたことある?
Yeah.
うん
Show me your face being licked.
舐められてる顔いっぱい見せてよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
tickles?
くすぐったい?
Yeah.
うん
I asked her to lick all the sweat from my armpits.
脇汗全部舐めてもらって
It's full of twists and turns.
くねくね盛りてる
It's cute.
可愛いね
Raise your elbows more.
もっと肘上げてほら
Kuro-chan looks like he's having fun.
黒ちゃん楽しそうな顔してるな
tickles.
くすぐったい
You can also lick the opposite.
反対も舐めていいよ
I was looking at the camera the whole time.
ずっとカメラ見てて
All nipples are visible.
乳首も全部映ってるよ
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
yes.
はい
I want everything to feel good from behind.
後ろから全部気持ちよくしたいんだって
What about your breasts?
おっぱいどう?
Look.
ほら
Where are you being touched now?
今どこ触られてるの?
Tell me how you feel when you touch my neck.
しくび触られたら どういう気持ちになるか教えて
It makes me feel good.
気持ちよくなっちゃう
That's right.
そうなんだ
Something is still standing.
なんかもたってるけど
Shackle.
しくび
Please don't say it.
言わないでほしい
Can you see how hard it is?
固くなったの分かる?
By yourself.
自分で
Kuru-chan, this is the best chair.
くるちゃんこれ最高の椅子だよな
You can taste it all over your body now.
もう全身も 味わっていいからね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Good, Kuro-chan.
いいな、黒ちゃん
I'm sucking these boobs with this face on my face.
こんな顔でこのおっぱいしゃぶってるよ
Are your breasts being licked?
おっぱいペロペロされてる?
feeling?
気持ち?
Isn't it ticking, little one?
カチカチじゃねえか、ちくび
I want you to suck it into my mouth.
自分からちくび口の中に 吸ってもらえな
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
tits.
おっぱい
Make your little one stand up like this.
ちくびこんなピンピン立てて
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Let's see the most embarrassing part.
一番恥ずかしいところ見ちゃおうか
Where is it?
どこだろう?
Don't you understand?
分かんないの?
minutes
分か
No.
ん ない
You can slowly take off your pants.
パンツゆっくり脱いでもらえる
By yourself?
自分で?
If you ask Kuro-chan to take off her clothes, she might do something to you after she takes them off.
黒ちゃん脱がしてもらったら 脱いだついで何かされるかもし
I can't, but it's okay.
れない けど 大丈夫
Be careful there.
気をつけしてくださいそこで
I'll cover my hands.
手隠すのに
Have them handle it on the side.
横に手つけてもらう
Look at the camera.
カメラ見て
There's plenty of cake.
ケーキしっかりあるやん
My hands are in the way.
手が邪魔なんだよな
Be careful.
気をつけ
The camera is very close.
カメラめちゃくちゃ近くにあるけど
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's so erotic that you're growing.
気が生えてるのエロいね
Please don't turn away.
絶対そらないでね
Open your legs a little.
ちょっと足開いて
One more voice.
もう一声だ
I can't see it clearly.
見えそうでくっきり見えないね
I turned backwards.
後ろ向きになった
Leave the back fully exposed.
後ろもいっきり付け出して
Staring at the camera.
カメラ見つめて
Open your legs more.
足もっと開く
I can't see your pussy.
マンコ見えないよ
Open more.
もっと開いて
That's a small pussy.
ちっちゃいマンコだね
Sit there.
そこを座って
Do the physical education.
体育通りして
There.
そこで
both.
両方
That hand is getting in the way, so get out.
その手邪魔だから出て
Get this out.
これ出て
Open your legs.
足開いて
Hey, open your legs.
ほら足開いて
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm too shy to open my legs.
恥ずかしがって足開かないんだよ
I finally want that.
それがやっと欲しい
too
も
Come forward.
っと 前に来て
You're shy, Hikari-chan.
恥ずかしがりやだな、ヒカリちゃん
Open your legs.
足開くの
Are you doing a dangerous pose?
やばいポーズしてる?
Yeah.
うん
Erotic pussy.
エロいマンコ
Hikari-chan, look at the camera.
ヒカリちゃん見て、カメラ
My pussy is photographed very close up.
マンコめちゃくちゃアップで撮られてるよ
or
や
Ba.
ば
I'm taking a really close-up photo of her right now.
今 すんげードアップで撮ってあげてるからね
Oh no.
やば
Pussy.
マンコ
Kuro-chan, could you please spread this out?
ちょっと黒ちゃんこれ広げてもらえる?
No way.
やだ
Place it by hand.
手で置いて
Look at that beautiful face.
その綺麗な顔見して
How do you feel now?
今どういう気分?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
She has such a beautiful pussy.
すごい綺麗なマンコしてるよ
Oh no.
やば
It's twitching and cute.
ヒクヒクしてて可愛い
Kuro-chan, what should I do about this?
黒ちゃんこれどうしたらいいの?
Chew.
チューして
Well then, let's take a look.
じゃあちょっとチューしてみよっか
Really come here.
ほんとこっちおいで
Until the last minute.
ギリギリまで
Raise your feet.
足上げて
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
copper?
どう?
Hikari's pussy.
ヒカリちゃんのマンコ
It's really delicious.
めっちゃおいしいし
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Because it doesn't taste delicious.
美味しそうな味そうではないからな
Such a cute pussy.
こんな可愛いマンコ
Where are you being licked now?
今どこ舐められてる?
Oh no.
やば
Say it.
言って
Where in the pussy?
マンコのどこ?
like?
好き?
This is what I want to choo choo.
チューチューしたいなこれじゃん
He says he loves it.
大好きだって
That pussy looks amazing.
すんげーうまそうなマンコ
Kuro-chan, is he sticking his tongue in his little hole?
黒ちゃんこのさ、ちっちゃい穴にも 舌ぶち込んでる?
A wet pussy.
ぬれぬれのマンコ
A hole where you can put your tongue.
舌入れちゃう穴に
My pussy is being licked.
マンコ舐められてる
Look, my pussy juice is dripping.
マン汁垂れてきてるよほら
Look.
ほ ら
A huge pussy.
めっちゃのマンコ
Kuro-chan's pussy juice is dripping, so I'm licking it all up.
黒ちゃんマン汁垂れてるからさ、 それ全部舐めてる
It's delicious, isn't it?
美味しいでしょそれ
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
I can't hold back for a moment, so I make you lick my dick.
ちょっと我慢できないから舐めさせるかちんちん
Will you do that?
そうする?
Sit down.
座って
Hikaru-chan.
ヒカルちゃん
yes.
はい
There's something thick in front of me.
なんか目の前にもっこりしてるんだけど
Can I ask you to tell me the name of this?
この名前教えてもらっていい?
I don't know.
わかんない
Don't you know?
わかんないの?
yes.
そう
Kuro-chan, please show me that.
黒ちゃんちょっとそれ見せてやって
It's Veron.
ベロンだし
Did you understand this?
これでわかった?
What's this name?
これ名前何?
Don't you know?
わかんない?
Well then, let's have a little smell.
じゃあちょっと匂い嗅いでみようか
Maybe I'll remember.
思い出すかも
Smell this.
匂い嗅いでよこれ
What does it smell like?
何の匂いする?
insect?
虫?
Kuro-chan, let's put this on your face to remind you.
黒ちゃんこれ顔にペシペシ当てて思い出させよう
This is called chinchin.
これちんちんって言うんだよ
Don't you know?
知らないか
It has a naughty shape, right?
エッチな形してるでしょ
Warm.
あったかい
I've never had my face rubbed before.
顔こすられたことないでしょちんちんで
do not have.
ない
Kuro-chan, do the other side too.
黒ちゃん反対側もやって
Try them all.
全部やってみて
That's great, Kuro-chan has a cute face.
最高だね黒ちゃん可愛い顔に
Big shochinchin.
大きいしょちんちん
You're happy now, aren't you?
幸せでしょ今
Kuro Chankore, what happened to Chinchin?
黒 ちゃんこれちんちんどうしたの?
Open your mouth.
口開いて
Take out your tongue.
ベロ出して
While looking at me.
こっち見ながら
What do you do, Chinchin?
ちんちん何する?
Big.
おっきい
Is it big?
おっきい?
Do you prefer a big penis or a small penis?
おっきいちんちん、ちっちゃいちんちんどっち好きなん?
I like big ones.
おっきい方が好き
like?
好き?
So, is it okay to say that I like this dick?
じゃあこのちんちん好きってことでいい?
Yeah, I like it.
うん、好き
Then let me make you feel better.
じゃあもっと気持ちよくしてあげてよ
Try talking with your dick.
ちんぽしゃべってみて
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いじゃん
Can you tell me it's delicious?
ちんちんおいしいって言ってごらん?
Can you say it?
言ってごらん?
It's so delicious.
ちんちんおいしいって
Isn't it delicious?
おいしいでしょ?
What?
何が?
Say it.
言って
Chinchin delicious.
ちんちんおいしい
Talk while looking at me.
見つめながらしゃべって
Let's bring out Peron.
ペロンをいっきり出して
Because it's balls.
タマタマだから
He licked me all the way to the top.
ペ ロンって上まで舐めてきて
superior?
上?
I also licked his balls a lot.
タマタマも舐めていっぱい
I'll lick all the balls into my mouth.
タマ全部口に舐めるだから
It's filled with sperm.
そこに精子がいっぱい詰まってんだよ
Is it all in your mouth?
口に全部入ってる?
Tama Tama.
タマタマ
I'm licking a really naughty place.
すごいエッチなとこ舐めてる
That's huge, Chin-chan.
でっかいね、ちんちゃん
Spit on me.
ツバ垂らしてさ
Squeeze.
しこしこして
While staring at me.
こっち見つめながら
Shut up and look at me.
しこしこして、こっち見て
copper?
どう?
I'm sure it's a place where you can get excited.
きっとパンパンってするところじゃん
It's ticking, Chin-chan.
カチカチだね、ちんちゃん
Who made it so hard?
誰のせいでこんな硬くなっちゃったの?
Add it all the way to the bottom.
一番奥まで加えて
Is it big?
大きいかな?
keep it up.
頑張れ
Stop all the way.
一番奥まで止まって
Is it painful there?
そこ苦しいの?
This way
こっち
Look.
見て
bully?
い じめる?
Then let's go get a pet.
そ したらペットいこう
Crow-chan, what do you want to do?
クローちゃん、どうしたい?
My boobs are being licked again.
またおっぱい舐められてる
It's Chikibipinpin.
チキビピンピンじゃん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Let's make it crunchy.
コリコリしてもらおう
Her pussy is fully visible.
マンコ丸見え
Crow-chan, let's spread it out once.
クローちゃん、一回広げようか
I'm taking it to the deep hole.
奥の穴まで取ってるよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's coming.
くりじってくるじゃん
Don't twitch.
ピクピクしちゃダメ
It's so wet.
すごい濡れてるよ
That's tough, Crow-chan.
きっついだろ、クローちゃん
18 year old tight pussy.
18歳のキツマンコ
What's in your pussy?
マンコ、何入ってる?
refer to.
指
Are you being stirred up?
かき回されてるの?
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
Have your own legs.
自分で足持って
Show me your pussy.
マンコ見せつけて
Kuchu ku chu ku chu.
くちゅくちゅくちゅ
Ippa
いっぱ
Let me stir it.
い かき回してもらいます
It's all taken out, even the asshole.
ケツ穴まで全部取れてるから
Open your legs.
足開いて
Look here.
こっち見てごらん
It feels really good.
すごい気持ちよさそうじゃん
I can feel it a lot.
感じちゃうの、いっぱい
You can't run away, come on.
逃げちゃダメ、ほら
You can't run away.
逃げちゃダメだよ
Show me where you go with your pussy.
おマンコで行くとこ見せてごらん
You can't run away, come on.
逃げちゃダメだよ、ほら
It feels good, so let me show you.
気持ちいいから見せてごらん
Is it dangerous?
やばいの?
Show me where you're going.
行くとこ見せてごらん
Show me, here.
見せてね、ほら
Let's go, let's go
いっちゃう、いっちゃ
cormorant.
う
This is Manjuren.
マ ンジュレンです
It's too slimy to pick up.
ぬるぬるすぎて拾わない
It's wet.
ぬれぬれだね
It's dangerous to use.
やばいの使う
Should I put a plump cock in it?
ふっといチンポ入れるか
What, it's moving?
何これ、動いてる
Do you know?
知ってる?
This is a vibe.
これバイブ
Maybe I should know.
知っとくかも
I'm going to fuck you tight now.
今からこのきついお前をぶち込むから
Hold your legs and be yourself.
足抱えて、自分で
Show me all your pussy.
お マンコいっぱい見せて
I swallowed it all.
飲み込んじゃったよ、全部
I went all the way in.
奥まで入っちゃったよ
This sucks really well.
すんげー吸いついてくんね、これ
My pussy is tiny.
おマンコ、ちっちゃくて
Do you like to put something hard in it?
固いの入れるの好きでしょうか?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
I can't have you make a mess.
ぐちゃぐちゃしてもらえない
It's dripping so much juice.
すごい汁垂れてるな
It's dripping from my pussy.
めちゃくちゃマンジで垂れてきてる
I'm tired again.
また疲れたんだよ
I won't stop until I go again.
また行くまでやめないから
また行くまでやめないよ
Did you go again?
また行ったの?
I'm twitching so much.
めちゃくちゃピクピクしてる
Even if it's too wet, it won't spread.
ぬれぬれすぎても広がらないんだよ
Manjul is dripping.
マンジュル垂れてきちゃうの
Can't you bear it anymore?
もう かまんできないか
It's tiny and cute.
ちっちゃくちゃかわいい
Show me a lot.
いっぱい見せて
Have them lick you a lot.
いっぱいエッチに舐めてもらう
This is bigger than the original one.
元帰りよりチンチン大きくなる、これ
Hikari-san's pleasant mouth makes me hard.
ヒカリさんの気持ちいい口でカチカチにしてもらう
Make people lick it.
人をペロペロにして
Suck it up.
それを吸って
With a cute face.
かわいい顔で
Give me a lot of licking.
いっぱい舐めてあげて
What do you want the cloture to do?
クローチャーは何してほしい?
Have it covered.
かぶりついてもらう
You like to make dick feel good, right?
チンチン気持ちよくするの好きでしょ?
Show me a lot.
いっぱい見せて
It looks delicious and I eat it.
おいしそうにチンチン食べるね
Give me a lick with cloture.
クローチャーと舐めてあげて
I want you to ride on top.
上に乗ってほしい
You want me to lick you, right?
おまえをペロペロしてほしいでしょ?
I want Chin Chin to wake up more on this side.
チンチンもっとこっち側に起こしてほしい
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Hika
ヒカ
Ri-chan's butthole is completely visible.
リ ちゃん、お尻の穴まで丸見える
The manjiru also looks amazing.
まんじるもすごい出てるし
Sometimes I wet it with my tongue.
たまにベロで濡らしてあげて
Lick that big dick a lot.
いっぱい舐めて、そのでっかいチンチン
Talk to me for a while.
しばらくまで喋ってよ
It sticks from the cloture's tongue.
クローチャーの舌からついてほら
You can't go anymore.
もういっちゃダメだよ
Make you feel good.
気持ちよくする
Cloture, do it again.
クローチャー、もう一回やれ
That's painful, Chin Chin.
苦しいね、チンチン
Your face is cute.
可愛いよ、顔
Even the suffering face.
苦しんでる顔も
Huge dick.
でっかいチンチン
What do you do, cloture?
どうする、クローチャー?
Do you want to cum in Hikari-chan's small pussy?
ヒカリちゃんの小さいおまんこにぶち込む?
good?
いい?
Hikari-chan.
ヒカリちゃん
Do you want to put it in your pussy?
お まんこにぶち込む?
Strap on top.
上またまってする
Take it yourself.
自分で持って
I might get in.
入るかも
Too big?
でかすぎる?
Let's do our best.
頑張ろう
Did you win?
勝った?
The cloture is also too big.
クローチャーもでかすぎる
copper?
どう?
This chin chin.
このチンチン
big.
大きい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
This is the best cloture.
クローチャー最高だね、これ
He's tight and has this face.
キツマンで、この顔
Because it looks delicious and naughty.
うまいやらしいからだ
Your pussy is full of dick, isn't it?
おまんこ、チンチンでパンパンでしょ
I like big dicks.
大きいチンチン好きだもんな
Is it possible to see where it's stuck?
ぶつ刺さってるとこ丸見えだと?
This is tough, isn't it?
キツイでしょ、これ
It's really tough.
めちゃくちゃキツイ
This is terrible.
やばいな、これ
It's erotic to move your hips by yourself.
自分で腰動かしててエロいじゃん
She looked like she couldn't help but want to have my cock inside her.
チンポ入れたくて仕方ない顔して
Hikari-chan, look at this.
ヒカリちゃん見て、これ
Look at your pussy, cock.
おまんこ見て、チンポ
It's stuck in my pussy.
おまんこ刺さってる
appear?
見える?
You have a hard cock stuck in your body.
カチカチのチンポ刺さってるでしょ
Please make my pussy all messed up.
いっぱいまんこ、ぐちゃぐちゃにしてもらえな
Down, down, down.
下、下、下
Look here.
こっち見て
This is such a bad tongue.
そんないけないベロだね、これ
Try smoking this.
これちゃん、吸ってみな
Try smoking a choo choo.
チューチュー吸ってみな
I want you to buy them all.
全部買って欲しいんだよ
This is delicious, isn't it?
おいしいでしょ、これ
Ah, yay
あー、や
times.
ばい
Have them follow you all the way to the back.
奥 までいっぱいついてもらう
Ah, the feeling
あー、気持ち
good.
いい
My legs are really shaky.
足 すんごいビグビグしてる
This hair is amazing.
すんごい、この毛だ
Erotic.
エロい
That's naughty.
やらしいな
That feels good.
気持ちよさそう、それ
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
This one hits the nail on the head, right?
奥当たるでしょ、これ
What is Kore-chan's specialty?
これちゃんの得意はどう?
Manjul looks like it's dripping.
マンジュル垂れてるような
yes.
はい
I'm under heavy pressure.
強圧にビグビグしてるよ
Have both hands on you.
両手ついてもらう
Do you like Oku?
奥好き?
like.
好き
I'll have a lot of them.
いっぱいついてもらう
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
Oh my god, it feels so good.
や ばい、気持ちいい
This one is more accurate, right?
こっちのほうが当たってるでしょ、
that.
それ
Do you like bags?
バック好きなの?
Yes, I like it.
はい、好き
Hikari-chan's head is standing up.
ひかりちゃん、首も立ってるよ
There may be a symposium in there.
シンポ入ってるかもしれん
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Please add more.
もっといっぱいついてください
Go ahead, push yourself to the limit.
もう、してごらん、限界まで
I just can't do it anymore.
もう、できないで、ちょっと
Do it now, people.
もう、してごらん、人が
Is there a symposium?
シンポ入ってるかどうか
Please pierce my pink pussy.
ピンクのおまんこ、ぶっ刺さってきて
Hikari-chan, please be more excited.
ひかりちゃん、もっとパンパンついて
It's amazing, it's so easy and the best.
すごい、気安くて最高だね
Apply it with manjul, dick.
マンジュルで塗るのだよ、ちんちん
Does it feel that good?
そんな気持ちいい?
It feels so good, Kuro-chan.
めちゃくちゃ気持ちよさそう、くろちゃん、
this.
これ
Manjul is dripping.
マ ンジュルが垂れまくってる
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Manjul, you're doing great.
マンジュル、すごいよくなってる、
this.
これ
It felt so good.
気持ちよすぎて
I went all over and my juices dripped all over it.
行きまくって、汁垂れまくっちゃった
Kuro-chan, your dick is terrible.
くろちゃん、ちんこやばいわな
My stomach is really big, but I'm tingling.
お腹すごい、ヒクヒクいってるけど
It makes me twitch.
ピクピクしちゃうね
I'm feeling bloated.
た まパンパンになってる
Progress feels good.
進歩気持ちいいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I can't stand it.
我慢できないんだ
Do you like normalcy?
正常意好き?
like.
好き
It feels good, it looks cute.
気持ちよさそう、かわさそう
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Hikari-chan, I'm going to cum inside your pussy.
ひかりちゃん、おまんこの中出すから
Hikari-chan, let's take it out.
ひかりちゃん、出しちゃうよ
Hikari-chan, I'm sorry.
ひかりちゃん、ごめん
I took everything out.
中全部出したわ
Karuchinkona.
かるちんこな
Why do you twitch?
なんでピクピクしちゃう?
It's so jiggling.
すんげープルプルしてんじゃん
Because my sperm is still sluggish.
まだ精子だるくあるから
This is fine.
これでいいじゃん
Paint it in the first place.
そもそも塗って
Because I covered Hikari's pussy with cum.
ひかりちゃんのまんこ、精子まみれにしたから
I put out a lot.
いっぱい出しちゃった
This is because Hikari-chan's pussy is so messy.
これさ、ひかりちゃんのまんこでくっちゃくちゃになったから
You can have everything cleaned.
全部きれいにしてもらえる
Suck it clean.
しゃぶってきれいにして
A little too good to be true.
ちょっと、うますぎて
This feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ、これ
Even though I released sperm, it became this big.
精子出したのに、こんなでっかくなっちゃったよ
Next, Pero.
次、ぺろで
It was beautifully done.
きれいにできた
Karu-chan.
かるちゃん
How was your day?
今日どうだった?
It was embarrassing.
はずかしかった
Was it embarrassing?
はずかしかった?
But for some reason, it was extremely embarrassing.
でもなんか、恥ずかしい割合めっちゃいっきまくってた
Because it felt good.
気持ちよかったから
Her pussy felt amazing.
すんげー気持ちよさそうなまんこしてたもん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Let's hide again this time.
また今度隠れてやろうよ
good?
いい?
Promise me.
約 束ね
Well then, thank you for today.
じゃあ今日はありがとう
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Bye-bye Karu-chan.
か るちゃんバイバイ